Finding aid for Bentley Historical Library records, 1919 - 2014
Bentley Historical Library
- Division Records
  - Preservation and Conservation, 1987-2004
    The Preservation and Conservation series (1977-2010, 2.3 linear feet) contains two subseries, Microfilm Projects, 1987-2010 (2.2 linear feet) and Reports, 1977-2007 (0.1 linear foot). The Microfilm Projects subseries consist of two alphabetic sequences that span different time periods (1987-2004) and (2000-2010). They were created by archivist Ann Flowers as she prepared individual collections for microfilming. They contain correspondence with the microphotography contractors and her quality control and cost analyses. The records are in alphabetical order by collection name.
    - Microfilm Projects, 1987-2004
      - Payment Logs, 1989-2004 (Box 34)
      - Status Sheets, 1991-2004 (Box 34)
      - 9th Infantry, 2003 (Box 34)
        (Abbott, Butler, Conely, Converse, Cooley, Harter, Hathaway, Kapp, Kelley, Springsteen, White Watrous)
      - 16th and 17th Infantry, 2002 (Box 34)
        (Barrett, Heald, Stockton, Quartermaster, Van Hoosen, Visher, Comstock, Enos, Hulbert, Maltman, Martin, Milmes, Moore, Saffor, Shepard, Watts, Webb)
      - Alumnae Survey, 1924; 2003 (Box 34)
      - Anderson, John, 1994 (Box 34)
      - Austin, Judson, 2000-2001 (Box 34)
      - Bailey, Franklin H., 1997-1998 (Box 34)
      - Bandholtz, Harry Hill, 1994-1997 (Box 34)
      - Barbour, Chadwick, Harriman, 1st Infantry Reg. Co. F Quartermaster, 2000-2001 (Box 34)
      - Bethel AME Church (Detroit), 2000-2001 (Box 34)
      - Bingham, Kinsley, 2000 (Box 34)
      - Boughton, Anderson, Brethschneider, Butterworth, Hodskin, Hume, Jessup, March, Mogk, Randall, Setright, Sutton, US Army, Mich 2nd Infantry Co. C, 2000-2001 (Box 34)
      - Boyce, Noll, Cutcheon, Boston, 1999 (Box 34)
      - Buck Family, 1999-2000 (Box 34)
      - Christiancy, Isaac Peckham, 1998-2000 (Box 34)
      - Civil War Portrait Collection and Robert Crouse, 1999-2000 (Box 34)
      - Convis, Orville: Grand Truck Railway System, 1998-1999 (Box 34)
      - Crapo, Henry How, 1991-1993 (Box 34)
      - Curwood, James Oliver, 1989-1990 (Box 34)
      - Davis Family, 1997-1998 (Box 34)
      - Dean, Henry Stewart, 2004 (Box 34)
      - De Land Family, 2003 (Box 34)
      - Drew, Walter, 1992-1996 (Box 34)
      - Faxon, John and James Fisher, 2000-2001 (Box 34)
      - Ferry Family, 2004 (Box 34)
      - German Christian Agricultural and Benevolent Society of Ora Labora, 1994 (Box 34)
      - Graham, Walter, 1993 (Box 34)
      - Grant, Claudius Buchanan, 1999 (Box 34)
      - Green, Sullivan Dexter, 1999-2000 (Box 34)
      - Griffin, Eli, 2001-2002 (Box 34)
      - Griswold Family, 1997-1998 (Box 34)
      - Hampton, Will, 1998-2000 (Box 34)
      - Haydon, Charles B., 1992 (Box 34)
      - Howe, George, 1998 (Box 34)
      - Joy, Henry, 1990 (Box 34)
      - Kellogg, John Harvey, 1989 (Box 34)
      - Kelsey Museum of Anthropology and Thomas Spencer Jerome, 2001 (Box 34)
      - Kidd, James Harvey, 2004 (Box 34)
      - Kresge, Sebastian Spering, 1993-1995 (Box 34)
      - Kresge, Stanley, 1993-2001 (Box 34)
      - Ladies Aid Societies, 1989-1990 (Box 34)
      - Lehman Family, Association of 20th Michigan Volunteer Infantry, Field, Greene, Kingsley, Long, McArthur, Short, 2000-2001 (Box 34)
      - Leonard, Donald, 1989 (Box 34)
      - Leuthenser, Margaret, 2000-2001 (Box 34)
      - Lockley, George, 1998 (Box 34)
      - Love, John, 2003 (Box 34)
      - Michigan Historical Records Survey, 1987-1990 (Box 34)
      - Michigan Historical Records Survey Processing Notes, 1987-1990 (Box 34)
      - Michigan Supreme Court-Michilimackinac, 1997 (Box 34)
      - Military Order of the Loyal Legion of the United State Michigan Commander, 1997-1998 (Box 35)
      - Monteith, John, 1998 (Box 35)
      - Morey, Adams, Cobb, Fyfe, Hutchinson, Jelley, Townsend, 2001 (Box 35)
      - Murphy, Frank, 1991-1998 (Box 35)
      - Murphy, Frank, Inspection, 1991-1995; 2 folders (Box 35)
      - Noble, Alfred, 2000-2001 (Box 35)
      - Parkhurst, John Gibson, 2003 (Box 35)
      - Penn Central Transportation Co., 1991-1992 (Box 35)
      - Phelps, Edgar, Irwin Family, Moore Family, 2000 (Box 35)
      - Post Family, Orlando Carpenter, Henry Albert Potter, 1999 (Box 35)
      - Presbyterian Church: Lake Superior and Petoskey, 1990 (Box 35)
      - Redford Record, 1993-2003 (Box 35)
      - Richardson, Jonas D., Edwin Gilbert, John Bancroft, James Houghton, James Tuttle, Lauren Ripley, 1998 (Box 35)
      - Robbins, Jerome, 2000-2001 (Box 35)
      - Robinson Family, Orvey Barrett, Ransom Bush, William Limbarker, Silas Sadler, Henry Stark Seage, Eli Lake Starr, Edward Taylor, Harvey Warner, Dwight Woodbury, 1998 (Box 35)
      - Rowe Family, 2000-2001 (Box 35)
      - Ryder Family, 2000-2001 (Box 35)
      - SS Kresge Co, 1993-1996 (Box 35)
      - Scripps, James, 1999-2000 (Box 35)
      - Second Baptist Church, Detroit, 1989 (Box 35)
      - Shattuck, Lucius, Russell H. Alcott, Henry Clay Christiancy, Michigan Infantry 1st Regiment Muster Roll, Stanard Family, 2001 (Box 35)
      - Signal of Liberty, 2001-2002 (Box 35)
      - Sligh Family, 2004 (Box 35)
      - Smith, Charles Spencer, 1990-1995 (Box 35)
      - Spaulding, Oliver, 2004 (Box 35)
      - Sterling twp., Macomb Co., 1992 (Box 35)
      - Stevens, William Collin and Victor E. Comte, 2001-2002 (Box 35)
      - UM Athletic Department Scrapbooks, 1991-1992 (Box 35)
      - UM Chronicle, 1993 (Box 35)
      - UM Medical Theses, 1995-2000 (Box 35)
      - Vandenberg, Arthur and Hazel, 1991 (Box 35)
      - Washtenaw County Census Records:, 1827; 1834; 1845; 1850; 1870; 1992-1993 (Box 35)
      - Watson, Edward, 2001 (Box 35)
      - Winchell, Alexander, 1989-1990 (Box 35)
      - Withington, William, 2000 (Box 35)
      - Woodruff, David and Charles, 2001-2002 (Box 35)
      - Zion Lutheran Church, Ann Arbor, 1993 (Box 35)
    - Microfilm Projects
      - Microfilm Projects
        - American Legion, 2008 (Box 69)
        - Bagley, J.M: Baird Family Papers, 2006 (Box 69)
        - Buchanan Family, 2005 (Box 69)
        - Cleague, Albert, 2008 (Box 69)
        - Cole, Hall, Horton, Lewis and Sleight Papers, 2006 (Box 69)
        - Ervay, George, 2004 (Box 69)
        - Hager Family, 2005 (Box 69)
        - Howell, Seymour, 2005 (Box 69)
        - Kay, John, 2005 (Box 69)
        - McCreery-Fenton Family, 2005 (Box 69)
        - Microfilm Projects done by military unit, 2000-2002 (Box 69)
        - Noble, Henry, 2005 (Box 69)
        - Redford Record, 2008 (Box 69)
        - St. Thomas Evangelical Church, 2008 (Box 69)
        - Signal of Liberty, 2007 (Box 69)
        - Soule, Harrison, 2005 (Box 69)
        - Spalding Family, 2007 (Box 69)
        - Spalding, Wilbur, 2006 (Box 69)
        - Williams, Thomas H., 2010 (Box 69)
    - Reports
      - Conservator's Annual Reports, 1977-1987 (Box 69)
      - Conservator's Annual Reports, 2005-2007 (Box 69)
      - Conservator's Bi-monthly Reports, 1975-1989 (Box 69)
  - University Archives and Records Program (UARP), 1973-2004
    The University Archives and Records Program (UARP) series, 1973-2004, bulk 1981-2004 (7.5 linear feet) records are divided into five subseries: Agendas and Minutes, Marjorie Barritt, Nancy Bartlett, Staff Files and Manuals.
    The Agendas and Minutes, 1988-2004 subseries (0.5 linear feet) contains records of periodic staff meetings. UARP's first head, Marjorie Barritt, contributed records (2.3 linear feet) that evidence the germination of the UARP program, its evolution and growth from the 1980s to the late 1990s, and the development of records policy at the University of Michigan. Together with the records of her successor, Nancy Bartlett (0.8 linear feet) and electronic records archivist Nancy Deromedi found in Staff Files (5.5 linear feet), Barritt's subseries documents UARP's long continuing interest in addressing issues revolving around the archival management of electronic records. UARP's involvement with international archival issues, including Marjorie Barritt's and Nancy Bartlett's editorial management of a special issue of the American Archivist devoted to international archives, is also well documented. Nancy Bartlett's files also contain her records of teaching the practice of appraisal to archives students at the University of Michigan's School of Information.
    The Staff files subseries contains records generated by UARP staff, including assistant division head Brian Williams, electronic records archivist Nancy Deromedi, and associate archivist Marilyn McNitt. Brian Williams's files document the Bentley's work in advising the archives of the African National Congress University of Fort Hare in South Africa and the development of a collection strategy for documenting the history of medicine at the University of Michigan. The files of Nancy Deromedi, who later became head of the newly-formed Digital Curation Services division in 2011, document efforts to preserve and manage digital records, particularly the university's web presence and faculty and administration email. Marilyn McNitt's files include materials on exhibits planned by her as well as records relating to a project in which UARP provided the University of Michigan-Dearborn administration with consultation on records management and appraised and processed some of the Dearborn campus's records. The small subseries, Manuals, 1989-1994 (0.2 linear feet) includes instructions for UARP staff conducting field appraisal and processing collections. The unit's Records Policy and Procedures Manual 1993, was widely distributed throughout the university and is thus located in the "Bentley Historical Library Publications" record group, which has a separate finding aid.
    - Agendas and Minutes, 1988-2004
      - Administrative Committee, 1988-1998; 3 folders (Box 36)
      - UARP Staff Meetings, 1988-2004; 15 folders (Box 36)
        (Notes of Marilyn McNitt)
    - Marjorie Barritt, Division Head, 1973-1998
      - 5 year space projection, 1991 (Box 36)
      - Access to restricted files, 1988 (Box 36)
      - Alumnae Survey Project, 1996-1999 (Box 36)
      - Architecture policy, 1989 (Box 36)
      - Archiving Electronic Records Standard Practice Guide, 1996 (Box 36)
      - Asian-American Studies Conference, 1994 (Box 36)
      - Athletic Department, b, 1991; undated (Box 36)
      - Audio-visual audit and appraisal (including WUOM), 1993 (Box 36)
      - Confer project, 1991-1993 (Box 36)
      - Correspondence, 1983-1997 (Box 36)
      - Correspondence-internal, 1982-1994 (Box 36)
      - Correspondence-professional, 1981-1993 (Box 36)
      - Course Materials Policy, 1996 (Box 36)
      - Data warehouse, 1996 (Box 37)
      - Departmental Files Policy, 1988 (Box 37)
      - Digital needs of the Bentley, 1998 (Box 37)
      - Duderstadt papers, 1997-1998 (Box 37)
      - Electronic records, 1996 (Box 37)
      - Electronic records and technology planning and policy, 1983-1995; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Electronic records research and development conference, 1996 (Box 37)
      - Electronic Records/Standard Practice Guide, 1994-1997 (Box 37)
      - Faculty papers policy, undated (Box 37)
      - Fair use of digital images, 1994-1997 (Box 37)
      - Field procedures, 1989 (Box 37)
      - Field--Sample letters and transfer agreements, undated (Box 37)
      - Fieldwork and collection review, 1992-1998 (Box 37)
      - Financial records policy, 1983-1985 (Box 37)
      - Forms, undated (Box 37)
      - Freedom of Information Act Committee, 1973-1984 (Box 37)
      - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA): Presidential search, 1994-1995 (Box 37)
      - Fundraising at the University of Michigan (Development Education Program), 1992 (Box 37)
      - Gilman/Neurology oral history, 1997 (Box 37)
      - Group presentations to university units, 1994-1997 (Box 37)
      - Human Resource Development workshop on managing office records, 1985-1986 (Box 37)
      - Institute for Continuing Legal Education (ICLE), 1985 (Box 37)
      - Institute for Social Research (ISR) 50th Anniversary, 1997 (Box 37)
      - Institutional visits, 1996-1997 (Box 37)
      - International Council on Archives (ICA) 2nd European Conference, 1989 (Box 37)
      - International scene issue of American Archivist, 1989-1992 (Box 37)
      - International Symposium: "Archives without borders" in Maastrich, 1991 (Box 37)
      - Introduction to Archives Class re: UARP, 1996-1998 (Box 37)
      - Huron High interdisciplinary block (IDB), 1998 (Box 37)
      - "A League of Their Own: Founding of the Women's League and the Michigan League,", 1997 (Box 37)
      - Lipschutz, Susan (Associate Provost), 1995 (Box 37)
      - Managing records in digital formats, 1995-1997 (Box 37)
      - Managing records in e-mail systems, 1993-1995 (Box 37)
      - Medical class pictures, 1991-1996 (Box 37)
      - Medical-Human Gene Therapy Program, 1992-1994 (Box 37)
      - Medical scientist training program, 1989 (Box 37)
      - Medical units documentation--Brian Williams, 1994-1996 (Box 37)
      - Michigan Firsts: Leadership in Education (Annual Fund Coordinating Council), 1990 (Box 37)
      - Michigan Historical Collections as University Archives (Coffee with the faculty), 1983 (Box 37)
      - Michigan Media Argus vaults, 1987-1990 (Box 37)
      - Michigan Media Project, 1990 (Box 37)
      - Michigan Media, 1990-1991 (Box 37)
        (Friends Presentation 1990 and revisions for Annual Fund Coordinating Council)
      - National Elections Studies archival project, 1994-1995 (Box 37)
      - Patient files, retention of, 1989 (Box 37)
      - Philippines exhibit, 1983 (Box 37)
      - Planning documents for peer institutional survey, 1987-1988 (Box 37)
      - Planning for Athletic position, 1987-1992 (Box 37)
      - Planning, general, 1991-1995 (Box 38)
      - Policies, 1984-1988 (Box 38)
      - Polio project, 1996 (Box 38)
      - Processing guidelines, 1994-1996 (Box 38)
      - Processing-internal correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 38)
      - Processing returns, 1994-1995 (Box 38)
      - Proposals, 1988-1992 (Box 38)
      - Rationale and Charge for a University Committee to Reexamine the Role of the Bentley Library as Preserver of University Records and History, 1987 (Box 38)
      - Records Center Storage Policy, 1988 (Box 38)
      - Records Management Policy Development, 1988-1992 (Box 38)
      - Regent's Proceedings re: University Archives, undated (Box 38)
      - Science and Technology Appraisal of Faculty Papers, 1994 (Box 38)
      - Seals of the University of Michigan (Friends talk and online exhibit), 1995-1996 (Box 38)
      - South Africa Exchange, 1995-1997 (Box 38)
      - Special projects retreat, 1997 (Box 38)
      - Staff confidentiality agreement, 2000 (Box 38)
      - Statistics, 1981-1984
        - Accessions by month, 1987-1998 (Box 38)
        - Administrative requests, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
        - Processing, 1992-1993 (Box 38)
      - Steneck Conference on History of Health Care and Health Science in Michigan, 1991 (Box 38)
      - Student Records and FERPA, 1986-1987; 1997 (Box 38)
      - Student Records Policy, 1984 (Box 38)
      - Student Records U of M Unit Survey, 1979-1984 (Box 38)
      - Technology Committee/Hedstrom Report, 1996 (Box 38)
      - Technology Task Force, 1997 (Box 38)
      - UARP 5 year Report, 1986 (Box 38)
      - UARP Annual Reports, 1982-1991 (Box 38)
      - UARP Reports to Executive Committee, 1981-1985 (Box 38)
      - UARP Reports to Staff, 1982-1997; 2 folders (Box 38)
      - University of Michigan Electronic Records Project, 1986-1987 (Box 38)
      - University of Michigan History: Teaching, Research, Academic Student Life (Exhibit for Deans' Meeting), 1991 (Box 38)
      - University Records Program Activity Reports, 1979-1987 (Box 38)
      - University Women in the War (WWII) (for Development and Education Program), 1995 (Box 38)
      - Updates to the Bylaws of the Regents, 1997 (Box 38)
      - Upper Atmospheric Research Collaboratory, 1996-1997 (Box 38)
      - Vulcan, 1991 (Box 38)
      - Web-site Preservation, 1998 (Box 38)
      - You can find it at the Bentley: Documenting Famous Alumni (Development Education Program), 1993 (Box 38)
    - Nancy Bartlett, Division Head, 1998- (Box 39)
      - Appraisal Module Bentley Practicum
        - 1999-2000 (Box 39)
          [Student records restricted until July 01, 2085; removed to records center storage]
        - Appraising Academic Websites, 2001 (Box 39)
          [Student records restricted until July 01, 2086; removed to records center storage]
        - Faculty Websites, 2002; 2 folders (Box 39)
          [Student records restricted until July 01, 2087; 1 folder removed to records center storage]
      - Bentley Historical Library Records Survey, 2001-2004 (Box 39)
      - Bentley Historical Library Visual Resources Online, 1999 (Box 39)
      - Best of the Bentley Digital Images, 1998 (Box 39)
      - Campus Map Historical Tour, 1997 (Box 39)
      - China Leadership Forum: "University and China:, 1845-2006 (Box 39)
      - Electronic Mail Appraisal Report, 1999 (Box 39)
      - Duderstadt Project, 1997-2003; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - M-Pathways, 1998-1999; 3 folders (Box 39)
      - M-Pathways-MAIS, 2001 (Box 39)
      - Managing digitization projects, 1998 (Box 39)
      - My.umich.edu project, 2001 (Box 39)
      - Presentation to archives class, 1998 (Box 39)
      - Talks
        - At U of M presentation to Annual Fund Coordinating Council (AFCC), 1950s (Box 39)
        - Development, 1989; 2001 (Box 39)
        - Welcome Center, 1998 (Box 39)
      - UARP Website content, 2000-2002 (Box 39)
    - Staff Files, 1995-2004
      - Academic Websites, 2000-2001 (Box 39)
      - Bulletin Project
        - Reports and Research, 1999-2002 (Box 39)
        - Survey and Analysis of Selected University Publications: University Course Bulletin, Student Handbook, Course Schedule, 1999-2000; 2 folders (Box 39)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC) Electronic Records Policy, 2000 (Box 39)
      - Staff Files (cont.), 1995-2004 (Box 39)
      - David Wallace's Class Presentation, 2004 (Box 39)
      - Electronic Mail Appraisal Report, 1999 (Box 39)
      - Faculty Collections Report, 2003 (Box 39)
      - Nancy Deromedi, Associate Archivist
        - M-Pathways Project
          - General, 1995-1997 (Box 40)
          - General, 1997-2002; 2 folders (Box 40)
          - Reports, 1999-2001 (Box 40)
          - Student Services Appraisal, 1999; 2 folders (Box 40)
        - University of Michigan Web Documentation Strategy: Reports and Presentations, 2000-2003 (Box 40)
        - Year 2000 Project (Y2K), 1996-2001 (Box 40)
      - Brian Williams, Assistant Division Head, 1985-
        - Fort Hare, South Africa, Project, 1985-2003
          - General, 1996-2000; 3 folders (Box 41)
          - Archives Dedication Messages, 1998 (Box 41)
          - Azanian People's Liberation Army at the Truth and Reconciliation Commission, 2000 (Box 41)
          - Centre for Cultural Studies (now NAHECS), 1996 (Box 41)
          - Communications home to the Bentley, 1998-1999 (Box 41)
          - Finding Aids, 1998; 3 folders (Box 41)
          - Hedstrom recommendations for the establishment and organization of the University of Fort Hare archives, 2000 (Box 41)
          - Inside the ANC archives, undated (Box 41)
          - South Africa National Archives Annual Reports of the National Archivist and the State Herald, 1997 (Box 41)
          - University of Connecticut, 1998 (Box 41)
        - Little Big Horn College Archives Assessment (includes photographs), 2003 (Box 41)
        - Medical Project
          - Chemical Heritage Foundation, 1995 (Box 41)
          - Documentation, 1996-1997 (Box 41)
          - First open heart procedure, 1998 (Box 41)
          - Kellogg African American project, 1997-2000 (Box 41)
          - Organogenesis, 1996 (Box 41)
          - Patient records and privacy, 1985-1997 (Box 41)
        - Michigan on the March publicity, 1995-1996 (Box 41)
    - Manuals, 1992-1994; undated
      - Field Manual, 1994 (Box 41)
      - Processing Manual, 1992 (Box 41)
      - Processing Sound Recordings, undated (Box 41)
    - MeMail Project
      - Acquisition: Copy Method, 2010-2011
        - Analysis of pilots, .ZIP file
        - Development, .ZIP file
        - Internal Pilot Protocols, .ZIP file
        - Process and techniques, .ZIP file
        - Training materials, .ZIP file
      - Archival Description, 2011; .ZIP file
      - Bibliography, 2010 (Box 69)
      - Boegsted-Moeller, Daniel, 2010 (Box 69)
      - Cloud Services and Collaborative Tools, 2010-2011
        - Collaboration suite selection process, .ZIP file
        - Google transition team, .ZIP file
        - Postini, .ZIP file
        - Practice at other universities, .ZIP file
      - Digital Archives Development Plan, 2010; .DOCX file
      - Digital Processing
        - Resources and Procedures, 2010-2011; .ZIP file
          (Includes planning documents, policy proposals, workflow diagrams, metadata requirements, and programming needs)
        - Tool Testing, 2010-2011
          - Adobe Acrobat, .ZIP file
          - Aid4Mail, .ZIP file
          - AttachmentExtractor for Thunderbird
          - Digital Preservation Software Platform--Australian Archives, .ZIP file
          - Exchange managed folders, .ZIP file
          - EZDetach, .ZIP file
          - File Information Tool Set (FITS), .ZIP file
          - MessageSave, .ZIP file
          - RecMan, .ZIP file
        - Workflows and metadata extraction for email, 2010-2011 (Box 69)
      - File Format Research and Analysis, 2010-2011; .ZIP file
      - Financials, 2011-2012 (Box 69)
      - Interview
        - Summary Report, 2009 (Box 69)
        - Guidelines, Questions, and Reports, 2009-2011; .ZIP file
      - Job Aid, 2009 (Box 69)
      - Mellon Communications
        - 2009-2012, 2 folders (Box 69)
        - Various (Proposal and Reports), 2009-2011; .ZIP file
      - Minutes and Agendas, 2008-2011; .ZIP file
      - Policy Issues, 2009 (Box 69)
      - Presentations
        - Michigan Archives Association -- Deromedi and McKay, 2010 (Box 69)
        - Various, 2009-2011; .ZIP file
      - Proposal Bid Analysis, 2009 (Box 69)
      - Proposal from Advizex: Mimosa, 2009 (Box 69)
      - Proposal from EMC: Documentum (Box 69)
      - Proposal from IBM: FileNet, 2009 (Box 69)
      - Publications
        - "Lessons Learned from a Low-tech E-mail Capture Plan" (Midwestern Archives Conference Newsletter), 2013; .DOCX file
        - "The MeMail Project: Digital Curation at the Bentley Historical Library" (Midwestern Archives Conference Newsletter), 2011; .DOCX file
        - Partnering with IT to Identify a Commercial Tool for Capturing Archival E-mail of University Executives at the University of Michigan (SAA Campus Case Study 14), 2013; .PDF and .ZIP files
        - Will They Populate the Boxes? Piloting a Low-Tech Method for Capturing Executive E-mail and a Workflow for Preserving It at the University of Michigan (SAA Campus Case Study 15), 2013; .PDF and .ZIP files
      - Request for Proposals (RFP), 2009
        - Assessment of proposals, .ZIP files
        - Project management documentation, .ZIP files
        - Requirements gathering, .ZIP files
        - RFP Final version, .ZIP files
        - Schedules, .ZIP files
        - Technical Analysis, .ZIP files
        - Vendor Demos, .ZIP files
      - Storage
        - Interim and Long Term Planning Materials, 2010-2011; .ZIP file
        - Repository Options, 2009-2011
          - DeepBlue, .ZIP file
          - ImageNow
          - MailArchiva
      - Sharepoint (Box 69)
      - Sustainability, 2009 (Box 69)
      - University Library Collaboration, 2009-2011 (Box 69)